Guide to the Lewis and Clark Centennial and American Pacific Exposition and Oriental Fair Records 1894-1933
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- President's Office, Committee on Congresses (W. G. Eliot, Secretary), Series 5
  - Correspondence, general and colleges
    - Wakefiled, John - White, W. R., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 32/16)
      Warner, A.B. (Invitation to Open Discussion Following Frank Rigler)
      Warner, John DeWitt (Program, Conference on Civics)
      Washington, Brooker T., Tuskegee Institute, Alabama
      Washington School Journal, Olympia (Reference Conference Schedule)
      Waters, Frank M., Mayor, Salem (Delegates to Conference)
      Wellesley College, Wellesley, Massachusetts (Programs)
      Wells, J.L. (Copies of Provisional Program)
      Welsh, Herbert, Indian Rights Association (Unable to Attend Conference)
      Wesleyan University, Middletown, Connecticut
      Western Reserve University, Adelbert College, Cleveland
      Wheeler, Benjamin Ide, University of California (Program Educational Conference)
      Wheelwright, W.D. (Lead Discussion at Educational Conference September 2)
      White The Oregonian(Review of the Work of the Congress)
      White, W.A. (Decline Invitation to Speak)
      White, W.R., Loma Homestead, Point Loma, California (proposal for Theosophical lectures)
    - Wilbur, Earl M. - Withycombe, James, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 32/17)
      Wilbur, Earl M. (Prospectus)
      Wilder, Amos Parker (Speaker and Title)
      Wildes, Maurice H., Mayor, Everett, WA (Delegates to Conference)
      Williams, Brigadier General Constant (Unable to Attend)
      Willis, H.C., Echo, OR (Delegates to Conference)
      Wilson, J.R. (Reference Speaking at Conference)
      Wilson, Washington, Normal School, Bellingham, Washington
      Wilson, Woodrow, Princeton University (Decline Invitation)
      Winchell, A.N. (Dates of Engineering Conference)
      Wise, Rabbi Stephen S.
      Withycombe, James (Decline Invitation to Speak)
    - Woodruft, Clinton - Zinser, L. C., 1904-1905 (Box-folder 32/18)
      Woodruff, Clinton Rogers (Accept Invitation to Speak)
      Woodson, C.E., Morrow County, OR (Delegates to Civics Conference)
      Woodward, Calvin M., Washington University (Prospectus)
      Woolley, Mary E., Mount Holyoke College, South Hadley, Massachusetts
      The World's Work, New York
      Wright, Croix (Expenses New York to Portland)
      Yoder, Professor A.H., University Station, Seattle (Reference Program)
      Young, F.G., State University, Eugene, Oregon
      Zueblin, Professor Charles, University of Chicago
      Zinser, J.C., County Superintendent of Schools, Oregon City
    - Unidentified idems, 1905; undated (Box-folder 33/1)
  - Minutes of meetings, Committee on Congresses, 1904 Nov. 30-1905 Aug. 9 (Box-folder 33/2)
  - Report of the Committee on Congresses, 1905 Aug. 20 (Box-folder 33/3)
- Secretary's Office (Henry E. Reed), Series 6
  See also Division of Exploitation, below, for additional Henry E. Reed materials
  - Ackowledgement of invitations to opening day ceremonies, 1905 (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Correspondence re: invitations to laying of cornerstone, 1903 (Box-folder 33/5)
  - Correspondence with Gammans and Malarkey, General Counsel, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 33/6)
  - Henry E. Reed letterpress copybook, 1902-1903 Mar. 3 (Box-folder 33/7)
  - Henry E. Reed letterpress copybook, 1903 Mar. 3- Apr. 20 (Box-folder 34/1)
  - Lewis & Clark Exposition Company contracts, 1903 (Box-folder 34/2)
    Contracts with Evelyn Newman, I. N. Fleischner, and Henry Reed
  - List of distinguished persons to be invited to the ceremony of the formal opening, circa 1905 (Box-folder 34/3)
  - Record of Admissions, Compiled by Henry E. Reed, 1906 Jan. (Box-folder 106/1)
    "Statement in detail by months during the whole time that the gates were open to the public."
  - Secretary's reports, 1905 Dec. 5 (Box-folder 34/3)
- Division of Architecture (Ion Lewis), Series 7
  - Blueprints Of Selected Exposition Buildings, undated (Box-folder Oversize Folder)
    Administration Building—Floor Plan
    Location of Chutes (2 sheets)
    Observation Tower (unbuilt)
    Proposed Casino Building (John Carson, Architect)
  - Construction bids, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 34/5-7)
  - Construction bids—Tabulation of bids, circa 1905 (Box-folder 34/8)
  - Correspondence of Ion Lewis, 1903 Apr.-1904 Dec. (Box-folder 34/9)
  - Correspondence of Ion Lewis, 1905 Jan.-Oct. (Box-folder 35/1-2)
  - Specifications for Forestry Building, 1904 Feb. (Box-folder 35/3)
  - Specifications for other buildings, 1903-1904 (Box-folder 35/4)
    Includes Administration Building, Colonnade, Fire Station, entrances, exits, states' building.
- Division of Concessions and Admissions (John A. Wakefield), Series 8
  - Applicants for concessions, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 34/5)
    Ledger volume, including notes on special events, 1904-1905.
  - Bills Payable Ledger, Department of Admissions, 1905 May-Oct. (Box-folder 109/1)
  - Clippings, Oversize, 1905 (Box-folder 123/1)
    Article on "The Tallest Man on Record is Ustus Machnow"; and notice "President Goode Makes No Complaint: Recommends That Optical Co. Be Careful, But Finds No Fault."
  - Contracts for Facilities
    - Administration Building - Crane Company, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 35/6)
      Administrative Building Lease
      Allen and Gilbert-Ramaker Company (Provide Organs and Pianos)
      American Inn Company, McCready, J.T. (Hotel Business within Grounds)
      Artist's Packing and Shipping Company (New York City)
      Baggage and Omnibus Transfer Company (Price Quotes)
      Bennett, J.E. (Entrance at 28th and Thurman Street)
      Bennett, J.E. (Entrance/Exit Gates/Ticket Booths)
      Bennett, J.E. (Lattice Enclosures for Water Tanks)
      Burrell Construction Company (Band Stand)
      Burrell Construction Company (Dancing Pavilion)
      Burrell Construction (General bond #20008)
      Burrell Construction (Main Entrance and Shelter; Public Comfort Buildings; Fire Department Building; Liberal Arts Building; Agricultural Building; Foreign Exhibits Building; Forestry Buillding)
      Bushong and Company (Folders)
      Contract Company: Cook, John W., President (Deliver Gravel)
      Crane Company (Galvanized Wrought Iron Pipe)
    - DeCaprio, A. - Gregroy D., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 35/7)
      DeCaprio, A. (Furnish Music and Concerts)
      Diamond Sand Company (Gravel)
      Dick, A.B. and Company (Deliver One Edison Rotary Mimeograph)
      Diebold Safe and Lock Company (Provide Safe)
      Dierke, Charles, Dierke Musical Institute (Furnish Music and Concerts)
      Ellery, Channing (Furnish Music and Concerts)
      Engineers, Founders, Machinists (Cancel Contract for Installation Two Rotary Pumps)
      Foster and Kleiser (Post Hand Painted Posters, OR, WA, ID)
      Gauld and Kline Company (Agreement for Galvanized Pipe)
      Gregory, D.J. (Generators and Rheostats)
    - Griffith, W. R. - King, John, 1903-1905 (Box-folder 35/8)
      Griffith, W.R. (Concentrator Shed for USGS)
      Griffith, W.R. (Erect Building for Manufactures; Liberal Arts and Various Industries)
      Griffith, W.R. (Erect Emergency Hospital on Site)
      Hammond Manufacturing Company (Excavation)
      Heusner, Geo. F. and J.R. Bowles (Steel Pipe)
      Hinton, S.A. (Superstructure for Pumping Station)
      Kilbourne and Clark Company (Furnish 65 Thru Glower Nerst Lamps)
      Killfeather, Edward (Culvert Construction)
      Killfeather, Edward (Pumping Station)
      King, John and Sutton, A.L. (Construct Landing Dock and Barges)
    - Lundstrom, K. G. - Otten, George, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 35/9)
      Lundstrom, K.G. (Cement Paving on Landings)
      Lundstrom, K.G. (Cement Steps, Balustrade, Buttresses)
      Lynds, E.A. (Entrance at American Inn)
      Lynds, E.A. (Offices for Custom House in Agricultural Building)
      Lynds, E.A. (Shed Extension to Machinery Building)
      Lynds, E.A. (Wings to Machinery Building)
      Memo Reference Erection of Lewis and Clark Memorial Building (Gammas & Malardy)
      Meyer and Anderson (Two Toilet Buildings)
      Mutual Label and Lithographic Company (Price Quotes)
      National Cash Register Company (Deliver Cash Registers)
      Norris Safe and Lock Company (Safe)
      Northern Pacific Railway Company (Flume)
      Northern Pacific Railway Company (Lay Spur Track)
      Northern Pacific Terminal Company (Extend Track from Sherlock Street to Fair Grounds)
      Otten, George (Plants for the Fair)
    - Pacific States Telephone - Standard Electric Co., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 35/10)
      Pacific States Telephone and Telegraph Company (Exchange Subscription)
      Pacific States Telephone and Telegraph Company (Police and Military Switchboard)
      Pfluger, Frank: Henry Weinhard (Construct Water Tanks)
      Pipe Line Permit
      Portland General Electric Company (Furnish and Deliver Transformers)
      Portland General Electric Company (Install Motors)
      Portland General Electric Company (Provide Electricity)
      Portland General Electric Company (Provide Regular/Spherical Frosted Incandescent Lamps)
      Portland Hydraulic Stone (Construct Art Building)
      Remington Typewriter Company (Deliver Typewriters)
      Smyth & Howard (2,000 Cubic Feet of Dirt Fill)
      Standard Electric Company, Baird, J. E. (Wiring Administration Building)
      Standard Electric Company, Baird, J. E. (Wiring Auditorium)
      Standard Electric Company, Baird, J. E. (Wiring Manufacturers Building and Bridge of Nations)
      Standard Electric Company, Baird, J. E. (Wiring Mining building)
    - Tinker & DeGesen - Wetherell, L. B., 1903-1905 (Box-folder 36/1)
      Tinker & DeGesen (Basins, Cement Steps, Balustrasds, etc.)
      Tinker & DeGesen (Cement Fountain and Steps)
      Tinker & DeGesen (Cement Steps and Buttresses)
      Tinker & DeGesen (Construct Enclosure Railing for Esplanade)
      Tinker & DeGesen (Construct Enclosure Railing for Long Bridge)
      Tinker & DeGesen (Extension of Grand Stairway)
      Tuerck, I.K. (Deliver Light/Electrical Fixtures)
      Union Printing Company, Brown, H.C. (Print 200,000 Mailing Cards)
      Veitier, F.H. (Furnish Music and Concerts)
      Vickery, Atkins and Terry (Pictures and Frames)
      Wakefield, Robert (Bridge from St. Helens road to Bulkhead)
      Wakefield, Robert (Make/Install Bulkhead and Boat Landing)
      Wells Fargo and Company (Transport Paintings/Pictures Portland to New York)
      Western Clay Manufacturing Company (Sewer Pipe)
      Wetherell, J.B. (Wooden Flume Willamette River to Guild's Lake)
      Wise, Otto Irving (Provide Two Concerts Per Day by Royal Hawaiian Band)
  - Contracts for Concessions
    There may be several copies of a contract in the file. Some files contain only copies of contracts, not originals.
    - Abalone shell - Automobiles, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 36/2)
      Abalone Shell, Jewelry and Novelties, #90 (Bergman E., Los Angeles)
      Advertising Rocking Chairs (Chamberlin, Clare)
      Aerial Navigation, #43 (Clarkson, T.S.)
      Aerial Way (Potter, A.M. and Company with City of Kansas City)
      American Electric Novelty Manufacturing Company #69 (New York)
      Amusement (Jabour, George)
      Animal Show, #18 (Jabour, Geo J.)
      Art Leather Goods, #63 (Belmont, Mrs. M.A., St. Louis)
      Art Pictures (Barchus, Mrs. Eliza R.)
      Automatic Stamping Machine, #107 (Chance, N.H.)
      Automobile (Clarkson, T.S.)
    - Blackbutte Quicksilver - Buttons, Badges & Banners, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 36/3)
      Blackbutte Quicksilver Mine, #150 (Dennis, W.B.)
      Blue Grotto (Schmohl, Henry R.)
      Bolossy Kiralfy Venice Company, #19 (Transportation)
      Borden's Malted Milk, #130 (Borden's Condensed Milk Company)
      Bubble Guns, #104 (Pierson and Killits)
      Burns Cottage, #61 (Oregon Burns Cottage Association)
      Burnt Leather and Curio Goods, #111 (Stevens, Clara Hatch)
      Burnt Wood and Carved Wood Novelties, #67 (Wells, Miss Eva L.)
      Buttons, Badges and Banners (Pferdner, Paul)
    - California Lunches - Coin Rolling, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 36/4)
      California Lunches, #144 (Wilson, Chas. L.)
      California Radium Exhibit (Richmond, C.B., Los Angeles)
      Card Printing (Kilham Stationary and Printing)
      Cascade Garden and Terrace of States, #11 (Williams, W.F., St. Louis)
      Certificate of Visitation, #15 (Forsyth, O.W., Seattle, WA)
      Certificate of Visitation, #15 (Wright, Alfred T., Ballard, WA)
      Chinese Village (Young, Tom and Lee Mee Toy, San Francisco)
      Chocolate and Cocoa (Baker, Walter and Company)
      Cider, #105 (Evans, D.H. and Company)
      Cigars, Cigarettes and Smokers' Articles, #47 (Whorley, F.C.)
      Coin Rolling, #136 (Sperry, Ray D.)
    - Darkness and Dawn - Electrical Music, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 37/1)
      Darkness and Dawn (Bayliss, Edward M., St. Louis)
      Davenport Farms Exhibit, #38 (Davenport, Homer)
      Dermal Preparations (Cunningham, J. Vance)
      Diving Elks and the Educated Horse, Princess Trixie #17 (Barnes)
      Dover Manufacturing Company, #55 (Asbestos Sad Irons)
      Egyptian Mosque–Toilet Luxuries (Woodward, Clarke and Company)
      Electrical Music, #20 (Pacific Coast Telharmonic Company)
    - Face Creams - Fruits, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 37/2)
      Face Creams and Cosmetics (Saxe, Gertrude)
      Filigree Jewelry, #60 (Ehrke, Ernest)
      Filipino Exhibition Company, #126 Felder, Edmund A.) See also Philippine Exhibit
      Formosa Oolong Tea, #140 (Formosa Oolong Tea Company, Yumeta Kushibiki)
      French Café, #14 (Jabour, Geo.J.)
      French Jewelry and Sundries, #152 (Gazvini, S.)
      Fruits, #80 (Frankel, Bruno)
    - Galveston Flood - Gem Stores, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 37/3)
      Galveston Flood Company, #54
      Gamble Hinged Music (Gamble, W.M.)
      Gay Paree, #8 (Jabour, Geo. J.)
      Gem Stones, Mounted and Unmounted, #128 (Bell, George, Denver, CO)
    - Hardware Specialties - Hungarian Charda, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 37/4)
      Hardware Specialties, #151 (Sterling Hardware Company)
      Haunted Swing, #22 (Oregon Amusement Company)
      Hay and Feed, #155 (Westgate, G.A.)
      Holland House (Elzas, M., Amsterdam, Holland)
      Hotel, #2 (McCready, J.A., American Inn)
      Hungarian Charda, #48 (Fischer, Mor' E., Budapest)
    - Ice Cream Waffle Cones - Italian Jewelry, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 37/5)
      Ice Cream Waffle Cones and Soda Fountain (Hazelwood Cream Company; see also following folder for photographs)
      Indian Arrow Heads (Stewart, W.H., Goldendale, WA)
      Indian Curios and Relics, #73 (Miller, Chris)
      Indian Goods and Curios, #121 (Dockarty, A.J.)
      Indian and Mexican Textiles, etc., #122 (Benham, J.W., Arizona)
      Infant Incubator, #9 (Schenkein, Samuel and Couney, Martin A.)
      Ingersol Dollar Watches, #101 (Lipman Wolfe and Company)
      Italian Jewelry, Coral and Shell Goods, #127 (Borrelli and Vitelli)
    - Hazelwood Cream Co. Soda Fountain—Photographs, circa 1905 (Box-folder 115/1)
    - Japanese Ball Rolling - Klondike Mining, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 37/6)
      Japanese Ball Rolling, #147 (Japan Art Trading Company)
      Japanese Village, #16 (Kushibiki, Yureto, St. Louis)
      Jewelry, Souvenirs and Novelties (DeWitt, Hugo and Mayer, J.)
      Keyless Locks and PipeWrenches, Inc. #135 (Miller, J.B.)
      Kiralfy's Carnival of Venice (The Kiralfy of Venice Company)
      Klondike Mining Exhibit (Ames, Geo. E.)
    - Ladis Flying Airships - Laundry, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 38/1)
      Ladis Flying Airships, #129 (Ladis, L. and Company)
      Land of the Midnight Sun (Bayliss)
      Launch, Gondola and Rowboat, #3 (Truscott Boat Manufacturing Company)
      Laundry, #87 (Lewis and Clark Laundry Company)
    - Leather and Aluminum Goods - Luna, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 38/2)
      Leather and Aluminum Goods, #91 (Henrice, Wilham E.)
      Leather Goods, #10 (Grossman, Henry, St. Augustine, FL)
      Leather Goods and Souvenir Novelties, #109 (Raphael, Hannah)
      Leather Goods and Souvenirs, #77 (Ford, Geo.B.)
      Light Walking Canes, #141 (Benham, J.W.)
      Lincoln Log Cabin (Abraham Lincoln Exhibit Company)
      Lipton Tea Exhibit, #102 (Lipton, Thomas J., Chicago)
      Liquid Transfer Fluid, #149 (Wickland, C.F.)
      Luna, #58 (Jabour, Geo) Contract only; no correspondence
    - Mailing Card and Stationary - Mosaic Jewelry, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 38/3)
      Mailing Card and Stationary, #19 (Rich, B.B.)
      Mammoth Mule, #157 (Emerson, Luke M.) Contract only; no correspondence
      Mann Hold-Fast Screw-Driver, #137 (Mann Speciality Company)
      Martin Chair Cane, #133 (Martin Chair Cane Company)
      Medical Lake Salts, #108 (Medical Lake Salt Manufacturing Company, Spokane, WA)
      Merchandise Sales, #120 (Lucas, Geo. F., Manufacturing Company)
      Merchandise and Souvenirs, #148 (Weiss, Max and Goldgraber, Jacob)
      Milk, Cream, Buttermilk and Ice Cream, #142 (Hazelwood Cream Company)
      Mirror Maze, #75 (Akoun, Fernand)
      Morocco Village (Hobbs, G.W. and Danforth, A.H., St. Louis)
      Mosaic Jewelry (Getzler, S.B.)
    - Niagra Falls - Optical, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 38/4)
      Niagara Falls (A Trip to Niagara Falls Concession Company)
      Novelty Concession, #49 (Hayward, Jas.T.)
      Official Catalogue, #64 (Hess, Albert)
      Official Guide, #21 (Bradley, Lawson)
      Official Photographer, #1 (Kiser Bros.)
      Official Program (Leiter, C. and Hess, Albert)
      Official Stationary (See: Mailing Card and Stationary, Rich, B.B)
      Old Plantation, #70 (Imes, Geo. E.)
      Optical (Owen, John B.
      Optical, #103 (Reed, Walter)
    - Parcel Checking - Pyrographic, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 39/1)
      Parcel Checking, #110 (Crabill, John)
      Parcel Checking and Messengers (Joy, Allen R.)
      Pedometers (Saterlee, J.P.)
      Peninsula Restaurant, #52 (Piehl, Henry G.)
      Penny Arcade, #70 (Bren, H.C.; Weiss, Max; Goldgraber, Jacob)
      Perfume Vending Machines, #106 (Miller, Geo. O.)
      Philippine Exhibit, #126 (Felder, Edmund) See also Filipino Exhibit Company
      Philippine Exhibit (McCowan, S.M.; Hunt, J.K.; Simms, S.C.)
      Phrenology, #156 (Griffith, H.T.) (No contract; only correspondence)
      Picture and Music Machine Arcade (Mechtler, Gustav)
      Pocket Cutlery, #51 (World Knife Company)
      Popcorn, Peanuts, Candy and Chewing Gum (Pacific Coast Biscuit Company)
      Printing of Engravings on Paper & Silk Handkerchiefs, #154 (Muir, Chas. S.) No contract, correspondence only
      Pyrographic, Taxidermy and Shell Goods (Tobias, Chas. C.)
    - Ralston-Acme Cereals - Ruby & Green Glassware, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 39/2)
      Ralston-Acme Cereals (Acme Mills Company)
      Ramona Belt Pins (Spicer, Mande C.)
      Restaurant (Kruse, Theo)
      Restaurant, #5, Bismarck Café (Mueller, Otto)
      Roast Beef Sandwich (Bayliss, Edward M.)
      Roller Chair, #6 (Clarkson Concession Company)
      Roltair's Haunted Castle and Trip to Venus, #62 (Roltair Company)
      Ruby and Green Glassware Engraved, #57 (Taylor, B.M.)
    - Saddlery and Carved Leather - Shell, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 39/3)
      Saddlery and Carved Leather, #131 (Garcia, G.S.)
      Sea Shells and Sea Shell Novelties, #66 (Averill, D.M. and Company)
      Seating, #7 (Clarkson, T.S., Portland Concession Company)
      Shears, Scissors and Razors (Claus Shear Company)
      Shell, Leather and Burnt Wood Novelties and Souvenirs, #79 (Miller, Maggie W.)
    - Shoe Shining - Smoked Eye-Glasses, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 39/4)
      Shoe Shining and Lavatories, #89 (Morey, R.G.)
      Shooting Gallery, #72 (Berkowitz, L. and Company)
      Silk Loom, #132 (Mrs. Mannion, J.J.)
      Silk Looms and Silk Machinery, #115 (Walker, Mrs. M.M.)
      Silver Goods and Jewelry, #138 (Providence Silversmith Company)
      Sistine Madonna Done in Needlework, #39 (Ripberger, Matilda)
      Smoked Eye-Glasses and Spectacles, #81 (Frankel, Bruno; see also folder series "Publications—Maps" for location of Frankel booths)
    - Soft Drinks, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 39/5)
      Soft Drinks, #125 (Barnes, W.J. and Whorley, F.C.)
      Soft Drinks, #118 (Bishwati, Kaalil)
      Soft Drinks (Davis, Glen L.)
      Soft Drinks, #59 (Hall, G.W. and Moore, W.A.)
      Soft Drinks, #82 (Mittey, R.and S.)
      Soft Drinks, #68 (Wescott, W.D.)
      Soft Drinks, #139 (Whorley, F.C.)
      Soft Drinks, #143 (Wilson, Chas. L.)
    - Souvenir Coin - Streets of Cairo, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 40/1)
      Souvenir Coin (Zerbe, Farran)
      Souvenir Spoon (Watson, Clarence L.)
      Souvenirs and Novelties, #112 (Cullen, R.P.)
      Souvenirs and Novelties (Ekberg, L.J.)
      Souvenirs and Novelties, #117 (Fleischman, Max)
      Souvenirs and Novelties, #123 (Grunebaum, A.)
      Souvenirs and Novelties, #146 (Mannion, J.J.)
      Souvenirs and Novelties, #71 (Saidy, A.T.)
      Souvenirs and Novelties, #65 (Seward, W.H.)
      Souvenirs and Novelties, #145 (Wilson, Chas. L.)
      Souvenirs of Western Women, #124 (Douthet, Miss Mary Osborn)
      Streets of Cairo and Oriental Village (Akoun, Gaston)
    - Televue - Tripod, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 40/2)
      Televue (Fowler, J.B. See also series "Publications—General" below.)
      Temple of Mirth, #13 (Akoun, Fernand)
      Temple of Palmistry, #21 ( Dunton, Hermine E.)
      Tetley Tea (Tetley, Joseph and Company)
      Toboggan (Park Improvement Co., Philadelphia)
      Toy Balloons and Rubber Novelties (Wilson, Harry L)
      Tozier Indian Collection (Aiken, G.I; Munly, N.G.; Aitchison, John E.)
      Trained and Untrained Wild and Domestic Animals, Birds and Reptiles (N.Y. Animal Show Co.)
      Trip to Siberia, #86 (Great Siberian Railway Company)
      Tripod Weighing Scales, #134 (Sischo, A. and Barton, Joseph)
    - Trip to Niagra Falls, 1905 (Box-folder 40/3)
      Primarily correspondence and memos, plus draft contract.
    - Utah Souvenirs - YWCA, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 40/4)
      Utah Souvenirs and Mormon Church Publications (Goddard, Benjamin and Hull, Thomas)
      Walking Canes, #113 (Lee, Mathias)
      Water Chutes, #12 (Water Chutes Company)
      Welch Grape Juice, #74 (Welch Grape Juice Company)
      Weller Pottery, #116 (Weller, S.A.)
      White Slave or a Glimpse of the Haren (Shapiro, Esther A.)
      Wilhoit Springs Mineral Water, #56 (McLeron, F.W.)
      Wooden Puzzles and Souvenirs (Hall, August)
      Y.W.C.A. Association, #55 (Building Construction)
    - General, 1904-1905 (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Correspondence, general
    - Abel (German Village); Abendroth (Jewelry, Souvenirs), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/1)
    - Abbot (Parcel Checking); Abbot (Photograph pass), 1904 (Box-folder 41/2)
    - Abbot, T. P. (Pacific Coast Telharmonic Co.), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/3)
    - Abbott (lunch stand); Acme Mills Co. (restaurant), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/4)
    - Adams (fruits and melons); Acme Triturator (their goods), 1905 (Box-folder 41/5)
    - Adams (stereoscopic views); Admas (novelties), 1905 (Box-folder 41/6)
    - Adkinson (perpetual motion); Admissions, 1904 (Box-folder 41/7)
    - Advance Food Co. (mammoth steers); Aerial Circuit Pleasure Wheel (merry-go-round), 1905 (Box-folder 41/8)
    - Agnew (book Si Hayseed); Aiken, Mnuly and Aitchinson (Tozier Indian collection), 1905 (Box-folder 41/9)
    - Ainsworth, J. C. (general); Albert (shoe shining), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/10)
    - Albin (engrosser and designer); Akoun (Streets of Cairo), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/11)
    - Akoun (Temple of Mirth); Alaska-Klondike Exhibit Co. (placer mining exhibit), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/12)
    - Alexander & Co. (optical goods); Allbery (Frankfurts & sandwiches), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/13)
    - Alleigh (check of parcels); Allen (decorating co.), 1904-1905 (Box-folder 41/14)